# Paul Gonzalez

Phoenix, Arizona

□ (760)413-7411 | ■ paulgonzalezdev@gmail.com | 回 github.com/myfriendpaul | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/myfriendpaul

### **Profile**

I am a results-driven Software Engineer, who overcomes challenges with a smile and comedic relief. Having a growth mindset along with extensive experience with people and management, I aim to bring my ambition to the tech industry to produce viable, user-friendly, solutions-oriented applications.

## **Experience**

**General Assembly** 

Remote

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING FELLOW

July 2021 - October 2021

- Completed a Full Stack Software Engineering project-based intensive program that prepares students to build and design applications.
- OnlyStonks Web app that allows users to search for stocks with up to date market price using the MarketStack API. Stock charts are generated by parsing through the last 30 days of historical data. Javascript, HTML, CSS
- · Seent-It Created with full CRUD functionality utilizing the TMDB API that then feeds the Airtable API allowing users to add, remove and update their movie watch list. Javascript, React, CSS, Material UI
- Boom! Roasted Project Lead Designed and developed for a coffee company that manages inventory with user authentication. Implemented an AGILE workflow and pair programming to manage the team's productivity. Javascript, React, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Express
- It Only Goes Up Cryptocurrency tracker application that allows a user to register, search and add cryptocoins to their portfolio with up to date price information. Javascript, React, CSS, Ruby on Rails

T-Mobile Phoenix Arizona

MOBILE EXPERT May 2019 - October 2021

- Utilized key performance indicators to exceed sales targets by implementing new sales strategies.
- · Directed and supervised employees engaged in sales and inventory-taking.
- Sustained ongoing customer relationships by building rapport and trust.

Indio, California

AT&T

ASSISTANT STORE MANAGER October 2017 - May 2019

- Ranked #1 in the district and ranked 10 in the Greater Los Angeles area in 2018 by emphasising Business Solutions.
- · Oversaw store operations, managed and developed an award winning sales team by focusing on team dynamics and customer experiences.
- Received District Manager's Award based on performance for Q2 of 2018.

**Wells Fargo** Palm Springs, California

PERSONAL BANKER

January 2013 - February 2013

- Ranked among the top 10 personal bankers throughout the district within the first 3 months of entering the role.
- Managed portfolio of 50 Small Business clients with estimated annual revenue of \$2.5 million.

**Starbucks** Palm Springs

SUPERVISOR

July 2013 - December 2015

- Increased sales by 18% for 2014 fiscal year by identifying bottlenecks in production.
- Reduced operating costs through efficient use of resources.
- Coached and trained partners to achieve a high degree of company standards.

#### Education

#### Western Governors University

**B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE** January 2020 - March 2021

#### **General Assembly**

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION, SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

July 2021 - October 2021

# Skills

FrontEnd HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Material UI **BackEnd** Express, MongoDB, Ruby on Rails, Docker, PostgreSQL

**Programming** Javascript, Ruby, Node.js, Git

**Currently Working With** Python, Flask, Angular